<teams>
<teaminfo>
    <name>Cardiff CIty FC</name>
    <top_players>
        <player>
            <name>Mark Hudson</name>
            <shirtno>5</shirtno>
            <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Mark-Hudson1.jpg"/>

            <gallery>
                <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Mark-Hudson2.jpg" />
                <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Mark-Hudson3.jpg"  />
            </gallery>

            <description>
                <![CDATA[After spells at Fulham, Crystal Palace and Charlton Athletic, central defender Mark Hudson signed for Cardiff City in July 2009, making a quick impact at the club. Having flourished in the Welsh capital as Club Captain, Mark is a strong leader, both on and off the pitch. He is now in his fifth season as a Cardiff City player, having played a leading role in the Club’s continued progress under Malky Mackay. Without a doubt Mark was an integral part to the Bluebirds historic promotion to the top flight.]]>
            </description>
        <statistics poy="2006-Present" goals="11">
        <data key="Football League Championship winner" value="2012/13" />
        <data key="League Cup runner-up " value="2011/12" />
        <data key="First Cardiff City Captain in the Barclays Premier League"  />
        <data key="Cardiff City Player of the Year" value="2012/13" />
        <data key="Cardiff City Goal of the Season" value="2012/13" />
        </statistics>
        </player>

      <player>
        <name>Peter Whittingham</name>
        <shirtno>7</shirtno>
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Peter-Whittingham1.jpg"/>
        <gallery> 
	        <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Peter-Whittingham2.jpg"/> 
	        <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Peter-Whittingham3.jpg"/> 
        </gallery>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[Cardiff City’s second longest serving current player, Peter Whittingham joined the club in January 2007 from Aston Villa after progressing from a trainee to their Premier league squad. Known for his impressive creative skills from midfield, Peter made an immediate impression in South Wales and has been a first team regular since his arrival. With over three hundred appearances, he has remained an important and consistent part of the squad since Cardiff City’s Barclays Premier League promotion.]]>
        </description>
        <statistics poy="2007-Present" goals="65">
         <data key="17 international caps for England Under-21" />
         <data key="PFA Championship Team of the Year" value="2009/10, 2011/12, 2012/13" />
         <data key="Cardiff City Player of the Year" value="2009/10, 2011/12" />
         <data key="Football League Championship winner" value="2011/13" />
         <data key="League Cup finalist" value="2012/13" />
        </statistics>
      </player>

      <player>
        <name>David Marshall</name>
        <shirtno>1</shirtno>
        <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/David-Marshall1.jpg"/>
        <gallery> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/David-Marshall2.jpg"/> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/David-Marshall3.jpg"/> 
        </gallery>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[Having performed admirably with both Celtic and Norwich City, having played UEFA Cup football with the SPL giants, David Marshall joined Cardiff City in May 2009. The undisputed first-choice ‘keeper at the club in recent years, David played in each of City’s 46 League fixtures during 2012/13, keeping eighteen clean sheets. Having worked to establish himself as a Scotland international, he was considered by many to be the standout goalkeeper in the Championship – David’s undeniable qualities a key factor in securing top flight football in the Welsh capital for the first time in fifty one years.]]>
        </description>
            <statistics poy="2009-Present Day" goals="0">
                <data key="Joined Cardiff for £500,000" />
                <data key="Scottish Premier League winner"  />
                <data key="Scottish Cup winner"  />
                <data key="10 international caps for Scotland"  />
        </statistics>
      </player>

      <player>
        <name>Kim Bo-Kyung</name>
        <shirtno>17</shirtno>
        <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Kim-Bo-Kyung1.jpg"/>
        <gallery> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Kim-Bo-Kyung2.jpg"/> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Kim-Bo-Kyung3.jpg"/> 
        </gallery>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[Joining Cardiff City from J League Division 1 side Cerezo Osaka in the summer of 2012, South Korean international attacking midfielder Kim Bo-Kyung’s first taste of football in Wales came in the 2012 London Olympics at the Millennium Stadium in the Welsh capital. After a short period of integration, Kim quickly became a fan favourite, known for his quick thinking and skill on the ball. Having played a part in the club’s promotion to the top flight of English football, he scored his first Barclays Premier League goal against Manchester United on 24 November 2013, securing a late 2-2 home draw with an injury time headed equaliser.]]>
        </description>
            <statistics poy="2012 - Present Day" goals="3">
                <data key="Football League Championship winner" value="2012/13" />    
                <data key="Olympic Bronze medallist" value="2012" />
                <data key="international caps for South Korea" value="25" />
                <data key="International Goals"  value="3"/>
        </statistics>
      </player>

      <player>
        <name>Craig Bellamy</name>
        <shirtno>8</shirtno>
        <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Craig-Bellamy1.jpg"/>
        <gallery> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Craig-Bellamy2.jpg"/> 
        	<img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/players/Craig-Bellamy3.jpg"  /> 
        </gallery>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[Having played for household names such as Liverpool, Celtic and Manchester City to name a few, Cardiff City supporters were naturally delighted to see hometown hero Craig Bellamy sign on loan for his local club in 2010. His qualities were clear to all as the Bluebirds ran close, but ultimately missed out on promotion that year, though Craig was thankfully able to complete the job of securing Barclays Premier League football two years later, this time as a permanent signing under Malky Mackay. His professionalism and attitude has been embraced by fellow professionals as the club made the big step to the top flight for the first time in 51 years.]]>
        </description>
            <statistics poy="2010 – Present Day" goals="77">
                <data key="78 international caps for Wales" />
                <data key="PFA Young Player of the Year" value="2001/02" />
                <data key="Welsh Player of the Year" value="2007" />
                <data key="Football League Championship winner" value="2012/13" />
                <data key="League Cup Winner" value="2011/12" />
        </statistics>
      </player>
    </top_players>     
    
    <video src="" />
    
    <gallery>
            <item>
                <img src="/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/gallery/CardiffCity-Stadium1.jpg" alt="Cardiff City Stadium" />
                <description><![CDATA[Cardiff City Stadium is the newest facility in the Barclays Premier League, having been completed and opened in the summer of 2009. A versatile venue, the Club owned stadium has also hosted open air concerts, rugby union and competitive Welsh international football fixtures. In 2013, following promotion to the Barclays Premier League the Club announced plans to increase capacity to approximately 33,000 by redeveloping one stand over the course of the season ahead of proudly hosting the 2014 UEFA Super Cup, featuring the winners of the 2013/14 UEFA Champions League and the 2013/14 UEFA Europa League. The extra seats will make Cardiff City Stadium the eleventh largest in the Barclays Premier League.]]></description>
                <statistics>
                    <description><![CDATA[<span fontWeight="bold">Capacity:</span> 60,362 <br/><br/><span fontWeight="bold">Field Dimensions:</span> 105m x 68m<br/><br/><span fontWeight="bold">Surface:</span> Desso GrassMaster.]]></description>
                    <stat key="Capacity" value="60,362 " />
                    <stat key="Field Dimensions" value="105m x 68m" />
                    <stat key="Surface" value="Desso GrassMaster" />   
                </statistics>
            </item>
    </gallery>
    
 <timeline><![CDATA[/assets/teamsheets/cardiff/timeline/DidYouKnow.swf]]></timeline>

</teaminfo>
</teams>